

github.com/APelekh 203-705-8768 andrii.pelekh@gmail.com Green card holder

Andrii Pelekh

A highly motivated software developer with a huge passion for pushing my personal and professional limits. My previous experience is in the finance field where I acquired strong problem solving skills, high attention to details and the ability to take responsibility and achieve results. I have a Master's degree in Computer Systems and Networks and a huge desire to build up my career as a back-end developer. I recently completed a software development boot camp where I expanded my software development skills further. Now, I am excited to join a team where I can become a beneficial member and contribute my skills.

SKILLS

- · C#, .NET, SQL, MVC, JavaScript, jQuery, AngularJS, HTML5, CSS3 and Agile
- · Visual Studio, Windows, Microsoft Dynamics AX, QuickBooks, Crunch Time, MS Office
- · Fluent in Ukrainian, Russian and have an elementary proficiency in German

EDUCATION

01/2015 - 03/2015

SeedPaths

· Intensive professional and software development boot camp focused on teaching the fundaments of software development.

08/2014 - 12/2014

Front Range Community College

· Courses taken: Math, English, Introduction to PC Applications, Introduction to Information Systems GPA – 4.0

09/2005 -07/2010

Ternopil National Economic University | Ternopil, Ukraine

· Bachelor's and Master's degree in Computer Systems and Networks

EXPERIENCE

06/2014 – 01/2015 (contract)

Accountant | Arrow Electronics | Denver, CO

- · Maintained accounts with over a balance of \$1.5 million total
- · Provided over 100 settlement reports every week and resolved any related discrepancies
- · Created a macro which increased my team's daily performance by 10%
- · Organized a client contact list with over 5000 entries, restructured all irrelevant/duplicate entries and decreased list size by 10%

03/2014 – 05/2014 (contract)

Data Process Analyst | HomeServe USA | Norwalk, CT

- · Analyzed over 200 processed payments on a daily basis
- · Investigated and resolved payment exceptions which prevented future customer's complains
- \cdot Tested new system for finance transactions and helped to find glitches

06/2012 - 02/2014

Accountant | Carnival Cruise Lines | Miami, FL

- · Reconciled over 200 hundred purchase orders every week
- · Submitted detailed ship's daily expenses/income spreadsheets to 10 department heads
- · Assisted over 15 ship's departments by providing necessary information and answering queries

07/2010 - 04/2012

Project Developer/Account Manager | Step Company | Ukraine

- · Presented an electronic dictionary software to clients
- · Assisted on project development and helped with databases and user interface
- · Manually tested new software features to assure proper function and performance

CERTIFICATIONS

02/2015

Certified Scrum Master

01/2013

Excel 2007 Advanced

· Filtering and Sorting Data, Using Pivot Tables, Working with Functions, Using Data Analysis Tools, Automating with VBA Macros